Donald trump campaign it on the defense of this morning after a
week full controversies and comment broadcast...trump turn up the feud with the family
...soldier killed in iraq in the thing interview he
fielded denied russia's military involvement in ukraine...comment monday about sexual
harassment...backlash on duty prop reviewed indoors house big a paul ryan or
senator john mccain in their primaries and by...front that...support
...two republican congressmen and a prominent donor from
denied any trouble yesterday in florida.
So, I just wanted-to tell you the campaign is doing really well it's never been.
Stole well united as we started on june...I would say right
now at the best in terms of being united that it's been since we
began where doing incredibly well...eating.
Paul manafort chairman the trump campaign...the morning...interesting and newt gingrich is
...will week like this is going to be too far gone in order to catch up then
...that he wouldn't vote for clinton karl rove said that a bit more weeks like this as
I said there's a range of friendly bar taking place at this
time that suggest that it may be slipping time is of the estimate and more
week like this they make it impossible to catch up well that
...true there's plenty of time were...first week of august usually
campaign in historical terms don't even start till september we are
...august as a very aggressive month...which the trump yesterday was in
florida crowds of fifteen thousand people those are october crowds ...really
...we...dollar-fifty state directors this we...everybody's
deployed working we...the record...less...the eighty million dollars
...with nobels so this is all cash...cash on hand so, no, we're fairly
we're...comfortable what we are concerned comfortable where we are organizationally
we're not comfortable with is the narrative that the media seems to be taking which is which is building
a storyline of that the democrats are controlling the race the word feel
comfortable if you look at our messages this...going to be...change
...and all the polls...talk about change you're talking about a,
you know, the khan family...whole range of things they're not that change and not
about issues well we were talking about changes...way...we will be for the rest of this
...next week we'll be talking about economic plan you know, the khan family situation that
...was trying to talk about...the fact that they were caught up in something bigger than that...yet you
...about...the blue water...as we all...but what he was a
...to talk about was the issue with the war the...the...let
you agree...has been a very bad week for the trump campaign and how
did how are you guys able to ignore the dropping poll numbers
and the defection that are happening...poll numbers were expected...the democratic of
...expect...this...drop depends on which poll you look and you know,
we feel like in another week or...are going to even out we always thought that we had a bounce we knew
that democrats...and, in...you see in the situation...looks like an
...field but in two weeks we think that's going to even out...out there on a message which we will
be the framework of this election favors donald trump if we run the campaign that we're
...running...we think...going to win we don't plan on
...in august we plan awaited november...in that will become evident...campaign
deploys there's a lot going...the local levels that you're not seeing that he doesn't seem to appear to stay on
message though isn't an issue for you
...he thing the thing is he's new admit picked when he says...
impede like the other day...get talking about strong message on what's going on with this...
hundred-million-dollars...the...which is an...amount of money that was
...the for hostages that probably...right straight to have to the terrorists
...gives cash...gave four hundred billion dollars in cash to the
...the harbor of terrorism you can only imagine with that money went in
...in that same rally where he got on-message
hitting the obama administration on that point he also went off message...of rehash them
all controversies including the of split with
...meagan kelly...he went back to talking about the blood coming out of her
whatever
within helpful do you think from intercom yesterday to clarify which part of her body he meant when he said that
...a responsibility on both parts the media...the campaign and everybody understood
what the real messages were and that speech and...was talking about the iranian situation thought about the
...to decisions women that you watch that...the headline...going to be on the
...hundred-million that attack why do you have to go there why do you have to...on...issues and rehash
...old controversy we feel confident that is the issues are being hurt
the local levels we had ...still getting report at the national level because also local media coverage to
let emulate about mr trump not endorsing paul ryan
the front-page of the many of the paper today and then his vice-presidential running
mate disagreeing with him and thing I strongly support paul ryan
...you your republican a lifelong republican loyal
...support speaker ryan re-election...of the campaign
is chairman of the campaign we have campaign position like getting involved in
...close personal friend of mike pence...nominated...governor
pent-up republican convention provides president donald trump understood that relationship
...of course, you know,...your life-long republican
nominee for president in the path for years...the...paul ryan of
...speaker and I know after...be...candidate for president to
...really moa?
Back...talking to the...
The election and ball run jumping...and that
What I take...him to...paul ryan...hours
...he's going to support paul ryan...he does support...he said he's going to work with paul ryan
...there's no issue about that he didn't take a position in the primaries
...but...a position many primaries that the news...the
...working together to elect republican climbers...president and I think you
...see that digestion as you this question terms of your previewed
role I spent a fair amount of time as a reporter with
...putin in terms of an interview maybe five hours...together he constantly
said to me...cia and others were responsible for the overthrow of
...which in ukraine in here you believe...right on that...which
...conversation eh I think that the
machinations of ukraine a deal with a lot of geopolitics america wasn't
...thank indiana...children say they I think the people over to the
...but there's a lot more going out of that country?
I don't think that unicode which was the prove one person that you compute
the and if you look at...went up...way but,
what not a good...situation in ukraine is the geopolitics
...very interesting that you look at but the acquaintance in europe today
in europe today because...agreement that was negotiated primarily
by article which and frankly that I was the principle person looking the you writers to conversation
...another time thank you paul I think we should get back to your thing that donald
...paul ryan for president I think that very interesting
...not yet prepared to do it...it out correct which then
...paul ryan on?
To get dribble of moa.
...like having...table thank you very much for coming in today.